fuckbookdating.com 2010-02-28

# FuckBook Dating - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement**  
Your privacy is important to us. We want you to enjoy the site, and to feel comfortable with the practices that we use to protect your personal information. This Privacy Statement covers FuckBookDating.com's treatment of your personal information. This Statement does not apply to the practices of companies that FuckBookDating.com does not own or control, or to people we do not employ.

FuckBookDating.com is a FREE online community designed to introduce men and women with attractive singles that are looking for mutually beneficial relationships. We collect and use your personal information to operate the FuckBookDating.com website and deliver the services you have requested.

**Information Collection**  
In order to use this website, you must be an adult at least 18 years of age (or older if the lawful age in your state, nation, or locality, is higher than 18); you must read and agree to the Terms of Use; and you must complete a registration form. When you register with FuckBookDating.com, you are required to provide contact information (such as email address), unique identifiers (such as username and password), and demographic information (such as birth date, gender, zip code, etc.). You may cancel your membership at any time by using our cancel page.

**Information Use**  
We use information you submit to help you create a personal profile and to help connect you with members with attributes identified by you as being important. Your profile and optional photo(s) are displayed on the site for public viewing and search by other members.

**Public Information**  
Public information you submit (such as gender, age, height, location, photos, etc.) is displayed in your profile and is meant to be viewed by the public. Photos and profiles must be approved by FuckBookDating.com to maintain the quality of the site. We monitor submissions to public areas by approving photos and profiles and reserve the right to monitor private areas if we suspect violation of the Terms Use. We reserve the right to remove, edit, delete or refuse any submission to a public or private area of the site.

We reserve the right to post reports of scam or deception received about those who have violated the Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement or the law or misused this website or other dating services for illegal or unethical purpose or monetary gain.

Profiles are public postings and may be spidered and indexed by search engines. FuckBookDating.com is not responsible for search engine listings. Members must protect their anonymity and not enter personal or business information in their username, headline, narratives, etc. which are for public viewing.

**Private Information**  
Private information (such as email address, IP address, zip code, birth date and time zone) is not displayed on the public areas of the site and is not available to other members. Email addresses are used to email account information and for marketing purposes. Zip codes are used to calculate distance between members. Birth dates are used to calculate age. (Age is displayed to other members.). 

We reserve the right to share your personal information (such as email address, IP address, zip code, birth date and personal interests) with third parties including but not limited to the selling of your complete profile information for use by third party dating sites.

**Information Automatically Collected**  
FuckBookDating.com automatically receives and records information from your browser including your IP address, browser type and cookie information. Your IP address is a series of numbers which identify your computer. We use it to help maintain our site. It does not provide personally revealing information about you.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small files stored by your browser in your computer while you visit our site. We use cookies to improve our site and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information when you change pages on the site. We use session cookies that are automatically deleted after each visit. Most browsers will accept cookies until you change browser settings to refuse them.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you are on the website. The companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites to provide ads about goods and services of potential interest to you. FuckBookDating.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers. Personal information may also be shared for survey purposes.

**Security**  
FuckBookDating.com follows reasonable technical and management practices to protect the confidentiality of information stored on our system. Your FuckBookDating.com account is password-protected for your privacy and security. If you have reason to believe that your account is no longer secure, you must promptly change your password by clicking on the 'Edit Account' link on the left side of your Member Home page.

**User Submissions**  
Be aware that any personally identifiable information you choose to disclose on this site, in public on your profile or in private through email to other members, is done at your own risk and that it may be collected or used by others. Caution and good sense should always be used in disclosing your personal identity to others and in selecting the type of information that you post on the website or release to others. FuckBookDating.com is not responsible for the use of any personal information that you may choose to disclose while on or off the website.

**Jurisdiction**  
This website may be viewed from many locations. Nonetheless, you agree that FuckBookDating.com is a Wisconsin based website and as such complies only with US, Federal and Wisconsin state laws.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
FuckBookDating.com will disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law, if necessary to protect the personal safety of users or the public, to protect and defend the rights or property of FuckBookDating.com, or if we find that your actions on our website violate the FuckBookDating.com Terms of Use. We are not responsible for death, personal injury, pain and suffering, loss of work or any other loss suffered by your use of this site.

**General**  
By using the FuckBookDating.com site, you agree to this Statement and the Terms of Use. We may change this Statement by posting a new version on our site and a notice of the change. We encourage you to periodically review this Statement in order to be informed of how FuckBookDating.com is protecting your information. You agree to sign a non-electronic version of this document upon our request.

If you have a privacy question about our site, please [contact us](mailto:support@fuckbookdating.com).
